Guide to the South Sheffield Hall, Yale University, Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
South Sheffield Hall, Yale University, photographs
1814-1931
RU 699
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
The materials consist of photographs and pictures of South Sheffield Hall at Yale. Included are photographs by photographers de Silva and Pach Bros.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-B (YRG 46-B), Records and materials documenting individual Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs and pictures of South Sheffield Hall at Yale. Included are photographs by photographers de Silva and Pach Bros.
Photographs; Yale College (1718-1887). Sheffield Scientific School; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University. Sheffield Scientific School
- Photographs, Series I
  - General views
    - 1814-1873 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 4)
    - -1865 (Box 1, Folder 5 - 6)
    - Drawings, 1865- (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1874-1879 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1874-1879 (de Silva, photographer) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - circa 1880-circa 1891 (Box 1, Folder 10 - 11)
    - circa 1886 (Pach Bros., photographers) (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1892-1901 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1901-1928 (Box 2, Folder 14 - 15)
    - 1920s (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - no date (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Interior views
    - Laboratory (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Tower apartment, 1887-1888 (Box 2, Folder 20 - 21)
    - Library (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Oversize view
    General note
    See RU 703